{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454510353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454510353"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454516642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454516642"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454521824","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454521824"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454530265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454530264"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454535276","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454535276"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454538664","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454538664"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454542311","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454542311"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454546659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454546658"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454553856","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454553856"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454557236","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454557236"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454562624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454562624"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454569723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454569723"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454574264","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454574263"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454577989","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454577989"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454581406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454581405"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454584974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454584974"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454588858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454588858"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454592791","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454592790"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454602412","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454602412"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454609892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454609892"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454614028","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454614028"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454619876","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454619876"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454623459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454623459"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454627504","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454627504"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454632375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454632375"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454637751","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454637751"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454643586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454643586"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 174eaac2-0783-4795-8877-d9f18bbf6707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454661370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454661370"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-1-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454668939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454668939"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-1-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454676129","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454676129"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454682317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454682317"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-1-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454692376","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454692375"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-6-8"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454709257","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454709257"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-9-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454716991","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454716991"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-9-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454723179","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454723179"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-4-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454729276","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454729276"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_7-6-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454735354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454735354"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_7-6-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454740726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454740725"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-7-8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454770321","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454770320"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_9-2-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454776355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454776355"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_9-2-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454783045","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454783044"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 5e14bc76-f047-480a-8749-d9061b0fa020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_2_9-2-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454798861","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454798861"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454800968","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454800968"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454803087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454803087"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454806303","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454806303"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454808530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454808530"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454810767","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454810767"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454813638","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454813637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454815847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454815846"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454818029","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454818029"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454821273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454821272"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454823378","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454823378"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454825471","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454825471"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454828434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454828434"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454830704","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454830704"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454832952","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454832951"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454835963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454835962"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454846712","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454846711"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454853529","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454853529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454864388","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454864388"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454866560","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454866560"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454868695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454868695"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454877804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454877804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454880127","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454880127"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454882375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454882375"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454885579","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454885579"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454888076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454888075"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454890580","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454890580"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454893857","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454893857"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454896156","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454896155"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454898457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454898457"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454901557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454901557"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454903781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454903781"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454908673","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454908673"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454911602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454911602"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454913984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454913984"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454916406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454916406"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454919690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454919690"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454922239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454922239"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454924707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454924707"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454927817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454927817"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454930148","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454930148"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454932547","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454932546"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454938624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454938624"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454940878","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454940878"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454943118","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454943118"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454946458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454946458"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454948860","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454948860"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454951273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454951273"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454954152","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454954152"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454956306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454956302"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454958450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454958450"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454961876","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454961875"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454964180","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454964180"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454966483","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454966483"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454969626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454969626"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454971859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454971859"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454974126","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454974126"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454977172","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454977172"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454979294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454979294"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454981410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454981409"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454984563","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454984562"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454986805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454986805"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454992179","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454992179"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454995444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454995443"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454997652","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454997652"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454999868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454999867"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455003161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455003161"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455005484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455005483"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455007784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455007784"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455010879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455010879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455013217","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455013217"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455015510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455015510"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455018898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455018898"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455019138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455019138"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_150131"," gameId":" 0d1cdedd-33bf-4828-8eda-6e47cccf3410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}